Finding Aid for Lutheran Church in America, Michigan Synod records, 1917-1987
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Lutheran Church Women
  - Michigan Synod (LCW:MS)
    - Activities
      - Visitation, 1969-1970 (Box 37)
      - Retreats, circa 1964-1970 (Box 37)
    - Newsletters-The Helping Hand (many issues missing), 1964-1972 (Box 37)
    - Leadership-Membership Development in Lutheran Church Women (1964 booklet) (Box 37)
    - Miscellaneous (unprocessed) (Box 37)
- Printed material
  The Printed material series includes newsletters and other publications of the Michigan Synod.
  - Michigan Synod Messenger, 1930-1962; 3 volumes (Box 16)
  - Outreach, 1963-1971 (Box 16)
  - Michigan Synod News, circa 1971-1980s (Box 16)
  - His, circa 1978-1980s (Box 16)
  - Today (LCA Convention news), 1962 (Box 16)
  - President's Pastoral letters (some gaps), 1962-1982 (Box 16)
  - Bishop's By-Line (beginning in 1983) (Box 16)
  - Books and other printed material (non-Michigan) (Box 38)
- Church files
  The Church files series is the largest in the Synod record group. Except for files of parochial and pastors reports, the series is arranged alphabetically by city, then name of church. The files include communications between the individual church and the Synod, financial and other reports required by the Synod, anniversary and other programs of events, and collected information. In the case of Hope Evangelical Lutheran Church of Detroit, the files also includes record books maintained by the church.
  - Parochial reports, 1963-1965 (Box 17)
  - Pastors reports (Box 17)
  - Adrian. Christ the Redeemer Lutheran Church (Box 17)
  - Albion. Grace Lutheran Church (Box 17)
  - Allegan. Immanuel Lutheran Church (Box 17)
  - Allen Park. St. Matthew Lutheran Church (Box 17)
  - Allen Park. St. Matthew Lutheran Church (cont) (Box 18)
  - Alpena. Grace Lutheran Church (Box 18)
  - Ann Arbor. Peace Evangelical Lutheran Church (Box 18)
  - Ann Arbor. Trinity Evangelical Lutheran Church (Box 18)
  - Baroda. St. John's Evangelical Lutheran Church (Box 18)
  - Battle Creek. Trinity Lutheran Church (Box 19)
  - Battle Creek. St. Peter's Lutheran Church (Box 19)
  - Bay City. Adoration Lutheran Church (Box 19)
  - Bay City. Messiah Lutheran Church (Box 19)
  - Belleville. Lutheran Church of the Apostles (Box 19)
  - Benton Harbor. St. Mark's Lutheran Church (Box 19)
  - Berkley. Gethsemane Lutheran Church (Box 20)
  - Berrien Center. Community Church (Box 20)
  - Berrien Springs. Lutheran Church (Box 20)
  - Big Rapids. Immanuel Lutheran Church (Box 20)
  - Birmingham. St. Andrew's Lutheran Church (Box 20)
  - Bloomfield Hills. Incarnate Word Lutheran Church (Box 20)
  - Brighton. Lord of Life Lutheran Church (Box 20)
  - Brown City Trinity Lutheran Church (Box 20)
  - Cadillac. Zion Lutheran Church (Box 20)
  - Cedarville. Bethel Lutheran Church (Box 20)
  - Charlotte. Peace Lutheran Church (Box 20)
  - Clarkston. Calvary Evangelical Lutheran Church (Box 20)
  - Clarkston. Calvary Evangelical Lutheran Church (cont) (Box 21)
  - Clinton Township. Epiphany Lutheran Church (Box 21)
  - Coldwater. Reformation Lutheran Church (Box 21)
  - Constantine. Messiah Lutheran Church (Box 21)
  - Dearborn. Hope Lutheran Church (Box 21)
  - Dearborn. Prince of Peace Lutheran Church (Box 21)
  - Detroit. Advent Lutheran Church (Box 22)
  - Detroit. Lutheran Church of the Atonement (Box 22)
  - Detroit. Augsburg Lutheran Church (Box 22)
  - Detroit. Augustana Lutheran Church (Box 22)
  - Detroit. Bethel Evangelical Lutheran Church (Box 22)
  - Detroit. Bethlehem Lutheran Church (Box 22)
  - Detroit. Christ Lutheran Church (Box 22)
  - Detroit. Christ Lutheran Church (cont) (Box 23)
  - Detroit. Cross of Glory Lutheran Church (Box 23)
  - Detroit. Church of the Cross Lutheran Church (Box 23)
  - Detroit. First Hungarian Lutheran Church (Box 23)
  - Detroit. Gloria Dei Evangelical Lutheran Church (Box 23)
  - Detroit. Good Shepherd Lutheran Church (Box 23)
  - Detroit. Holy Communion Lutheran Church (Box 23)
  - Detroit. Holy Trinity Slovak Evangelical Lutheran Church (Box 23)
  - Detroit. Hope Evangelical Lutheran Church
    - General materials (Box 39)
    - Record book, 1923-1951 (Box 39)
      - Volume 1, 1923-1931 (Box 39)
      - Volume 2, 1932-1939 (Volume 1)
      - Volume 3, 1940-1951 (Volume 2)
  - Detroit. Immanuel Lutheran Church (Box 24)
  - Detroit. Jehovah Evangelical Lutheran Church (Box 24)
  - Detroit. Jefferson Avenue Lutheran Church (Box 24)
  - Detroit. Luther Memorial Evangelical Lutheran Church (Box 24)
  - Detroit. Messiah Lutheran Church (Box 24)
  - Detroit. Olivet Lutheran Church (Box 24)
  - Detroit. Lutheran Church of the Reformation (Box 24)
  - Detroit. Evangelical Lutheran Church of the Resurrection (Box 25)
  - Detroit. St. John's Lutheran Church (Box 25)
  - Detroit. St. Paul's Lutheran Church (Box 25)
  - Detroit. St. Paul's Latvian Evangelical Lutheran Church (Box 25)
  - Detroit. St. Peter's Lutheran Church (Danish) (Box 25)
  - Detroit. St. Peter's German and Saxon Evangelical Lutheran Church (Box 25)
  - Detroit. St. Philip's Workers Lutheran Church (Box 25)
  - Detroit. Unity Evangelical Lutheran Church (Box 25)
  - East Detroit. Advent Evangelical Lutheran Church (Box 25)
  - East Detroit. All Saints Evangelical Lutheran Church (Box 25)
  - East Tawas. Grace Lutheran Church (Box 25)
  - Farmington. Antioch Lutheran Church (Box 25)
  - Farmington. Lutheran Church of the Incarnation (Box 25)
  - Fenton. Transfiguration Lutheran Church (Box 25)
  - Flat Rock. Faith Lutheran Church (Box 25)
  - Flint. Ascension Lutheran Church (Box 26)
  - Flint. Holy Trinity Lutheran Church (Box 26)
  - Flint. Lutheran Church of Our Risen Lord (Box 26)
  - Flint. Salem Lutheran Church (Box 26)
  - Garden City. Good Hope Lutheran Church (Box 26)
  - Gowen. Settlement Lutheran Church (Box 26)
  - Grand Haven. Lutheran Church (Box 26)
  - Grand Rapids. Ascension Lutheran Church (Box 26)
  - Grand Rapids. Bethlehem Lutheran Church (Box 26)
  - Grand Rapids. Faith Lutheran Church (Box 26)
  - Grand Rapids. Prince of Peace Lutheran Church (Box 26)
  - Grand Rapids. Trinity Lutheran Church (Box 27)
  - Grand Rapids. Unity Latvian Evangelical Lutheran Church (Box 27)
  - Grandville. St. Paul's Lutheran Church (Box 27)
  - Grayling. St. John's Lutheran Church (Box 27)
  - Greenville. Dannebrog Lutheran Church (Box 27)
  - Greenville. Trinity Lutheran Church (Box 27)
  - Grosse Ile. St. Thomas Lutheran Church (Box 27)
  - Hillsdale. Trinity Evangelical Lutheran Church (Box 27)
  - Ionia. Holy Cross Evangelical Lutheran Church (Box 27)
  - Jackson. Immanuel Lutheran Church (Box 27)
  - Jackson. St. James Lutheran Church (Box 28)
  - Kalamazoo. Our Redeemer Lutheran Church (Box 28)
  - Kalamazoo. Trinity Evangelical Lutheran Church (Box 28)
  - Kaleva. Bethany Lutheran Church (Box 28)
  - Kent City. Mamrelund Lutheran Church (Box 28)
  - Lake City. St. John's Lutheran Church (Box 28)
  - Lake Orion. King of Kings Lutheran Church (Box 28)
  - Lansing. Grace Lutheran Church (Box 28)
  - Lansing. Redeemer Lutheran Church (Box 29)
  - Lansing. St. Stephen Evangelical Lutheran Church (Box 29)
  - Leroy. Zion Lutheran Church (Box 29)
  - Livonia. Christ the King Evangelical Lutheran Church (Box 29)
  - Livonia. Holy Cross Evangelical Lutheran Church (Box 29)
  - Livonia. Resurrection Lutheran Church (Box 29)
  - Ludington. Bethany Lutheran Church (Box 29)
  - Ludington. Emmanuel Lutheran Church (Box 29)
  - Ludington. Victory-Trinity Lutheran Church (Box 29)
  - Madison Heights. Prince of Glory Evangelical Lutheran Church (Box 29)
  - Manistee. Good Shepherd Lutheran Church (Box 30)
  - Manistee. Messiah Lutheran Church (Box 30)
  - Manistee. Our Saviour Evangelical Lutheran Church (Box 30)
  - Manton. Trinity Lutheran Church (Box 30)
  - Marlette. Hope Lutheran Church (Box 30)
  - Marlette. Juhl, Zion Trinity Lutheran Church (Box 30)
  - Marshall. Mt. Hope Lutheran Church (Box 30)
  - Mason. All Saints Lutheran Church (Box 30)
  - Midland. St. Timothy Lutheran Church (Box 30)
  - Monroe. Christ Evangelical Lutheran Church (Box 30)
  - Monroe. Good Shepherd Lutheran Church (Box 30)
  - Montcalm County. First Lutheran Church (Box 30)
  - Mottville. Trinity Lutheran Church (Box 30)
  - Mt. Clemens. Bethlehem Lutheran Church (Box 30)
  - Mt. Clemens. Epiphany Lutheran Church (Box 30)
  - Mount Hope. Lutheran Church (Box 31)
  - Muskegon. Central Lutheran Church (Box 31)
  - Muskegon. Lebanon Lutheran Church (Box 31)
  - Muskegon. St. Luke's Lutheran Church (Box 31)
  - Muskegon. Samuel Lutheran Church (Box 31)
  - Niles. Holy Trinity Lutheran Church (Box 31)
  - Oak Park. St. Timothy Evangelical Lutheran Church (Box 31)
  - Olivet. Lutheran Church (Box 31)
  - Orchard Lake. Holy Spirit Lutheran Church (Box 31)
  - Orchard Lake. Redemption Lutheran Church (Box 31)
  - Oscoda. Hope Lutheran Church (Box 31)
  - Plymouth. Epiphany Lutheran Church (Box 31)
  - Plymouth. St. Michael Lutheran Church (Box 31)
  - Pontiac. Lutheran Church of the Ascension (Box 31)
  - Pontiac. Christ of the Lakes Lutheran Church (Box 31)
  - Pontiac. Gloria Dei Lutheran Church (Box 31)
  - Redford. Good Shepherd Lutheran Church (Box 32)
  - Rochester. Abiding Presence Lutheran Church (Box 32)
  - Rockford. St. Stephen Lutheran Church (Box 32)
  - Roseville. Bethany Lutheran Church (Box 32)
  - Roseville. Nativity Evangelical Lutheran Church (Box 32)
  - Saginaw. Resurrection Lutheran Church (Box 32)
  - Saginaw. Evangelical Lutheran Church of the Resurrection (Box 32)
    (include church record book, minutes of council meetings, and women's league meetings)
  - Saginaw. Our Saviour Lutheran Church (Box 32)
  - Saline. Faith Lutheran Church (Box 32)
  - St. Clair Shores. Triumphant Cross Lutheran Church (Box 33)
  - St. Joseph. Saron Lutheran Church (Box 33)
  - St. Joseph County. Moore Park Lutheran Church (Box 33)
  - Sidney. St. John's Lutheran Church (Box 33)
  - Southfield. Northwest Emmanuel Evangelical Lutheran Church (Box 33)
  - Southfield. Calvary Lutheran Church (Box 33)
  - Southgate. Holy Redeemer Lutheran Church (Box 33)
  - Southhaven. First English Lutheran Church (Box 33)
  - Stevensville. St. Luke's Lutheran Church (Box 34)
  - Sterling Heights. St. Thomas Lutheran Church (Box 34)
  - Sturgis. St. Timothy Lutheran Church (Box 34)
  - Taylor. Evangelical Lutheran Church of the Transfiguration (Box 34)
  - Tecumseh. Gloria Dei Evangelical Lutheran Church (Box 34)
  - Temperance. St. Paul's Lutheran Church (Box 34)
  - Three Rivers. St. John's Evangelical Lutheran Church (Box 34)
  - Traverse City. Bethlehem Lutheran Church (Box 34)
  - Trenton. St. Philip Lutheran Church (Box 34)
  - Troy. Lutheran Church of the Master (Box 34)
  - Tustin. Augustana Lutheran Church (Box 34)
  - Walled Lake. Shepherd of the Lakes Lutheran Church (Box 35)
  - Warren. Divinity Lutheran Church (Box 35)
  - Warren. St. Stephen Evangelical Lutheran Church (Box 35)
  - Waterford. Christ Lutheran Church (Box 35)
  - West Bloomfield. Holy Spirit Church (Box 35)
  - Westland. Holy Cross Lutheran Cross (Box 35)
  - Whitehall. Lebanon Evangelical Lutheran Church (Box 35)
  - Wyoming. Gethsemane Lutheran Church (Box 35)
  - Ypsilanti. St. Philip's Lutheran Church (Box 35)
  - Ypsilanti. Samaria Lutheran Church (Box 35)
- Miscellaneous subject files
  Miscellaneous subject files relating in part to the Synod's relationship with the Metropolitan Detroit Council of Churches and the Michigan Council of Churches have been arranged alphabetically into a Topical files series. Other topics in this series relate to organizational issues, to denominational groups, and to the seminaries of the denomination.
  - Applications of congregations for membership in the Michigan Synod (Box 12)
  - Auditor's reports (Box 12)
  - Chey appeal (Box 12)
  - Full-time president discussion (Box 12)
  - Hamma Divinity School (Box 12)
  - History "Prologue to the archives of the Michigan Synod; Background History of Lutheran Synods in America and tendencies toward union" by Lightner A. Swan (Box 12)
  - Metropolitan Detroit Council of Churches (Box 12)
  - Michigan Council of Churches (Box 12)
  - Michigan Synod Bicentennial Committee, 1974-1976 (Box 12)
  - Mulberry Home (Box 12)
  - New Lutheran School of Theology at Chicago, 1963 (Box 12)
  - Oesterlen (Box 12)
  - Pastoral letters, 1954 (Box 12)
  - Seminary merger (Hamma Divinity and Chicago Lutheran Seminary (Box 12)
  - Survey report and proposal to the Lutheran Church in America (Box 12)
  - United Lutheran Church in America (Box 12)
  - United Lutheran Church Men (Box 12)
  - United Lutheran Church Women (Box 12)
  - Wittenberg Women's Guild (Box 12)
  - Wittenberg University (Box 12)
  - Later materials and unprocessed (Box 46)
- Visual Materials
  The Visual Materials series consists of photographs, albums, and photographic negatives. This material is largely arranged alphabetically by place. Subjects include church buildings, events, and people associated with the various churches.
  - Photographs
    - Convention, Atlantic City, 1960 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Coordinating Convention, Salem Church (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Churches
      - Adrian (Box 43, Folder 3)
      - Albion (Box 43, Folder 4)
      - Allen Park (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - Ann Arbor (Box 43, Folder 6)
      - Battle Creek (Box 43, Folder 7)
      - B (miscellaneous)
        - Bay City (Box 43, Folder 8)
        - Benton Harbor (Box 43, Folder 8)
        - Berkley (Box 43, Folder 8)
        - Big Rapids (Box 43, Folder 8)
        - Brown City (Box 43, Folder 8)
      - C (miscellaneous)
        - Cadillac (Box 43, Folder 9)
        - Constantine (Box 43, Folder 9)
      - Dearborn. (Box 43, Folder 10)
      - Detroit. A-G (Box 43, Folder 11)
      - Detroit. Lutheran Church of the Cross, St. Jean and Charlevoix area; includes Tendler schools (Box 43, Folder 12)
      - Detroit. Hope Evangelist Lutheran Church (Box 43, Folder 13)
      - Detroit. Hope Evangelist Lutheran Church (with Rev. F. P. Madsen, individual and group shots) (Box 43, Folder 14)
      - Detroit. H-R (Box 43, Folder 15)
      - Detroit. S-Z (Box 43, Folder 16)
      - E-F
        - East Tawas (Box 43, Folder 17)
        - Farmington (Box 43, Folder 17)
        - Flat Rock (Box 43, Folder 17)
        - Flint (Box 43, Folder 17)
      - Garden City (Box 43, Folder 18)
      - Grand Rapids (Box 43, Folder 19)
      - G (miscellaneous)
        - Gilbert (Box 43, Folder 20)
        - Glenfield (Box 43, Folder 20)
        - Gowen (Box 43, Folder 20)
        - Grayling (Box 43, Folder 20)
        - Greenville (Box 43, Folder 20)
      - I-K
        - Ironwood (Box 43, Folder 21)
        - Jackson (Box 43, Folder 21)
        - Kalamazoo (Box 43, Folder 21)
        - Kent City (Box 43, Folder 21)
      - L
        - Lake City (Box 43, Folder 22)
        - Lansing (Box 43, Folder 22)
        - LeRoy (Box 43, Folder 22)
        - Livonia (Box 43, Folder 22)
        - Ludington (Box 43, Folder 22)
        - Luther Haven (Box 43, Folder 22)
      - M (1)
        - Madison Heights (Box 43, Folder 23)
        - Manistee (Box 43, Folder 23)
        - Marlette (Box 43, Folder 23)
      - M (2)
        - Marshall (Box 43, Folder 24)
        - Monroe (Box 43, Folder 24)
        - Muskegon (Box 43, Folder 24)
      - N-P
        - Niles (Box 43, Folder 25)
        - Oak Park (Box 43, Folder 25)
        - Oscoda (Box 43, Folder 25)
        - Plymouth (Box 43, Folder 25)
        - Pontiac (Box 43, Folder 25)
      - R-S
        - Rosemite (Box 43, Folder 26)
        - Roscommon (Box 43, Folder 26)
        - St. Clair Shores (Box 43, Folder 26)
        - Southgate (Box 43, Folder 26)
        - Southfield (Box 43, Folder 26)
      - T
        - Taylor (Box 43, Folder 27)
        - Tecumseh (Box 43, Folder 27)
        - Temperance (Box 43, Folder 27)
        - Three Rivers (Box 43, Folder 27)
        - Traverse City (Box 43, Folder 27)
        - Tustin (Box 43, Folder 27)
      - W
        - Walled Lake (Box 43, Folder 28)
        - Waterford (Box 43, Folder 28)
    - Miscellaneous (including camps) (Box 43, Folder 29)
    - Ordination & Other Rites (Box 43, Folder 30)
    - Personnel (Box 43, Folder 31)
    - Personnel (Box 43, Folder 32)
  - Albums
    - Small Album: Snapshots of churches in Detroit, Dearborn, Allen Park, Livonia and Michigan Synod Office Building (Box 43)
    - Large Album (snapshots of churches
      (arranged by name of county)
      - Bay County
        - Bay City (Box 43)
      - Genesee County
        - Fenton (Box 43)
        - Flint (Box 43)
      - Ingham County
        - Lansing (Box 43)
        - Mason (Box 43)
      - Kalamazoo County
        - Kalamazoo (Box 43)
      - Macomb County
        - East Detroit (Box 43)
        - Roseville (Box 43)
        - St. Clair Shores (Box 43)
        - Warren (Box 43)
      - Monroe County
        - Monroe (Box 43)
        - Temperance (Box 43)
      - Montmorency County
        - Gowen (Box 43)
  - Negatives
    (arranged alphabetically by name of county, then by city)
    - Alcona
      - Glennie, 2 items (Box 44)
      - Spruce, 7 items (Box 44)
    - Alpena
      - Alpena, 5 items (Box 44)
      - Ossinieke, 2 items (Box 44)
    - Arenac
      - AuGres, 2 items (Box 44)
      - Standish 5 (Box 44)
      - Sterling, 2 items (Box 44)
    - Barry
      - Woodland, 2 items (Box 44)
    - Bay
      - Auburn, 6 items (Box 44)
      - Bay City, 22 items (Box 44)
      - Essexville, 3 items (Box 44)
      - Kawkalin., 4 items (Box 44)
      - Monitor Township, 3 items (Box 44)
      - Munger, 4 items (Box 44)
    - Calhoun
      - Battle Creek, 5 items (Box 44)
    - Clinton
      - St. John, 2 items (Box 44)
    - Eaton
      - Grand Ledge, 2 items (Box 44)
    - Genesee
      - Clio, 2 items (Box 44)
      - Davison, 2 items (Box 44)
      - Durand, 2 items (Box 44)
      - Fenton, 4 items (Box 44)
      - Flint, 49 items (Box 44)
      - Flushing, 2 items (Box 44)
      - Grand Blanc, 2 items (Box 44)
      - Hadley, 3 items (Box 44)
      - Rankin, 2 items (Box 44)
      - Swartz Creek, 2 items (Box 44)
    - Gladwin
      - Gladwin, 5 items (Box 44)
      - Rhodes, 2 items (Box 44)
    - Gratiot
      - Alma, 10 items (Box 44)
      - St. Louis, 3 items (Box 44)
      - Wheeler, 3 items (Box 44)
    - Huron
      - Bad Axe, 2 items (Box 44)
      - Linkville, 3 items (Box 44)
      - Pigeon, 3 items (Box 44)
      - Sebewaing, 2 items (Box 44)
    - Ingham
      - East Lansing, 9 items (Box 44)
      - Okemos, 2 items (Box 44)
      - Lansing, 23 items (Box 44)
      - Mason, 4 items (Box 44)
      - Williamston, 5 items (Box 44)
    - Ionia
      - Ionia, 2 items (Box 44)
    - Iosco
      - Hale, 2 items (Box 44)
      - Tawas, 4 items (Box 44)
    - Isabella
      - Mt. Pleasant, 2 items (Box 44)
    - Kalamazoo
      - Kalamazoo, 4 items (Box 44)
      - Portage, 2 items (Box 44)
    - Kent
      - Wyoming, 1 items (Box 44)
    - Lapeer
      - Imlay City, 2 items (Box 44)
      - Lapeer, 4 items (Box 44)
      - North Branch, 2 items (Box 44)
    - Lenawee
      - Palmyra, 2 items (Box 44)
    - Livingston
      - Livingston (county), 2 items (Box 44)
      - Fowlerville, 2 items (Box 44)
      - Hamburg, 2 items (Box 44)
      - Howell, 4 items (Box 44)
      - Pinconning, 2 items (Box 44)
    - Macomb
      - Armada, 2 items (Box 44)
      - Disco, 2 items (Box 44)
      - East Detroit, 7 items (Box 44)
      - Frazer, 9 items (Box 44)
      - Macomb, 4 items (Box 44)
      - Mount Clemens, 16 items (Box 44)
      - New Baltimore, 5 items (Box 44)
      - New Haven, 4 items (Box 44)
      - Richmond, 5 items (Box 44)
      - Romeo, 1 items (Box 44)
      - Roseville, 8 items (Box 44)
      - St. Clair Shores, 20 items (Box 44)
      - Shelby (Township), 2 items (Box 44)
      - Sterling (Township), 5 items (Box 44)
      - Utica, 11 items (Box 44)
      - Waldenburg, 2 items (Box 44)
      - Warren, 32 items (Box 44)
      - Washington, 2 items (Box 44)
    - Midland
      - Midland, 3 items (Box 44)
    - Monroe
      - Dundee, 5 items (Box 44)
      - Ida, 8 items (Box 44)
      - Monroe, 23 items (Box 44)
    - Montcalm
      - Freedom (Township), 1 items (Box 44)
      - Trufant, 2 items (Box 44)
      - Other, 14 items (Box 44)
    - Muskegon
      - Muskegon, 2 items (Box 44)
    - Oakland
      - Berkley, 4 items (Box 44)
      - Birmingham, 15 items (Box 44)
      - Bloomfield Hills, 7 items (Box 44)
      - Bloomfield (Township), 2 items (Box 44)
      - Clarkston, 2 items (Box 44)
      - Clawson, 2 items (Box 44)
      - Drayton Plains, 2 items (Box 44)
      - Farmington, 18 items (Box 44)
      - Ferndale, 4 items (Box 44)
      - Hazel Park, 2 items (Box 44)
      - Highland, 4 items (Box 44)
      - Holly, 2 items (Box 44)
      - Lake Orion, 5 items (Box 44)
      - Madison Heights, 2 items (Box 44)
      - Milford, 4 items (Box 44)
      - Oak Park, 2 items (Box 44)
      - Orchard Lake, 2 items (Box 44)
      - Oxford, 8 items (Box 44)
      - Pontiac, 34 items (Box 44)
      - Rochester, 7 items (Box 44)
      - Royal Oak, 8 items (Box 44)
      - South Lyons, 6 items (Box 44)
      - Southfield, 15 items (Box 44)
      - Troy, 10 items (Box 44)
      - Walled Lake, 8 items (Box 44)
      - Waterford, 2 items (Box 44)
    - Ogenaw
      - West Branch, 2 items (Box 44)
    - Saginaw
      - Amelith, 2 items (Box 45)
      - Birch Run, 4 items (Box 45)
      - Brady (Township), 2 items (Box 45)
      - Bridgeport, 8 items (Box 45)
      - Carrollton, 1 items (Box 45)
      - Chesaning, 2 items (Box 45)
      - Frankenlust, 3 items (Box 45)
      - Frankenmuth, 4 items (Box 45)
      - Frankentrost, 2 items (Box 45)
      - Freeland, 4 items (Box 45)
      - Hemlock, 4 items (Box 45)
      - Ira, 2 items (Box 45)
      - Saginaw, 70 items (Box 45)
      - Swan Creek, 3 items (Box 45)
      - Zilwaukee, 2 items (Box 45)
    - Sanilac
      - Marlette, 4 items (Box 45)
    - Shiawassee
      - Owosso, 4 items (Box 45)
    - St. Clair
      - Algonac, 2 items (Box 45)
      - Capac, 5 items (Box 45)
      - Caro, 4 items (Box 45)
      - Fairgrove, 2 items (Box 45)
      - Marine City, 4 items (Box 45)
      - Marysville, 2 items (Box 45)
      - Millington, 4 items (Box 45)
      - Port Huron, 12 items (Box 45)
      - Richville, 1 items (Box 45)
      - St. Clair, 3 items (Box 45)
    - Tuscola
      - Mayville, 2 items (Box 45)
      - Reese, 6 items (Box 45)
      - Vassar, 4 items (Box 45)
    - Washtenaw
      - Ann Arbor, 22 items (Box 45)
      - Chelsea, 4 items (Box 45)
      - Dexter, 3 items (Box 45)
      - Ypsilanti, 4 items (Box 45)
    - Wayne
      - Allen Park, 4 items (Box 45)
      - Dearborn, 19 items (Box 45)
      - Detroit, 249 items (Box 45)
      - Garden City, 1 items (Box 45)
      - Grosse Pointe Farms, 2 items (Box 45)
      - Grosse Pointe Woods, 6 items (Box 45)
      - Hamtramck, 3 items (Box 45)
      - Highland Park, 2 items (Box 45)
      - Inkster, 2 items (Box 45)
      - Livonia, 25 items (Box 45)
      - Northville, 2 items (Box 45)
      - Plymouth, 7 items (Box 45)
      - River Rouge, 3 items (Box 45)
      - Southfield, 3 items (Box 45)
      - South Redford, 2 items (Box 45)
      - Wayne, 10 items (Box 45)
    - Other Locations
      - Illinois, 5 items (Box 45)
      - Ohio, 29 items (Box 45)
      - Franconia, 25 items (Box 45)
      - Indian Missions, 24 items (Box 45)
      - Miscellaneous, 3 items (Box 45)
  - Other Formats
    - X Pan Film
      - Germania, 4 items (Box 45)
      - Marlette, 4 items (Box 45)
      - Brown City, 3 items (Box 45)
      - Yale, 4 items (Box 45)
      - Greenwood Township, 3 items (Box 45)
    - Color Slides
      - Sault St. Marie, 4 items (Box 45)